(Lakshmi:)I'm gay.
(Leonard:)Like...
Dude-on-dude, but with women?
l know a fake marriage
isn't an honest way to live...
...but you, of all people, should know
how difficuIt it is to come out.
Why me "of all people"?
Well, there's a rumor
back in New Delhi that you're...
How shall we say?
(Lakshmi:)...comfortable in a sari.
(Raj:)- I'm not gay.
- Really?
(Lakshmi:)The chocolate lava cake,
the little soaps in the bathroom.
(Lakshmi:)And I'm sorry, but you're wearing
more perfume than I am.
(Raj:)That's Unbreakable by Khloe and Lamar.
(Raj:)And for your information, it's unisex.
Fill in the blank: "l love the nightlife..."
- l like to boogie.
- Got you.
(Raj:)With women. I like to boogie with women.
(Lakshmi:)That's disappointing. You were exactly
the kind of phony-baloney husband...
...l was looking for.
(Raj:)Thank you.
(Raj:)And once again, my baloney likes girls.